i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage
i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage
ما ابغى استنى يتحقق حلمي انا اروح له بنفسي
اكسر ام الـmen Runes مافي شي can mess with me
اسرق اي شي ثمين كأني طالع من عرين
احفر لو الكنز دفين حتى لو كان كمين
لو الحياة Game Sony men راح أختم
لو المود so hard مستحيل أستستلم
لو اللغة مو مفهومة برضو راح أترجم
لو اليد خربانة عادي عادي لأني راح أصدم
i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage
i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage
dig dig i make it wider
on them bits i'm a rider
i dig grave to my haters
i raise all of my faders
i put a use to my shovel
you should fear when i put your name here
in my list your name is going to rest
not taking it back
if i take it back then my game's not going last
brown's shovel up yo
i dont want the fame i just want the money
i be working hard y'all be acting funny
i dont take no aim i just shoot my shot
i just spray alot
and then i pray to god
i dont seek no fame i just want the money
i be working hard y'all be acting funny
i dont take no aim i just shoot my shot
spray alot
pray to god
i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage
i dont want single انا اخذ double
انا من الـHood انا معايا shovel
انا أشيل بالقوة  i dont f care
اسرق ام الـShow مكاني في Stage